<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  
    <title type="text" xml:lang="en">Sana Ajani</title>
    <link type="application/atom+xml" rel="self" href="http://localhost:3000/atom.xml"/>
  
  <link href="http://localhost:3000/"/>
  <id>http://localhost:3000/</id>
  <updated>2017-05-19T20:55:48Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Sana Ajani</name>
    <email>sajani6@gatech.edu.com</email>
  </author>
  <rights type="text">Copyright © 2017 Sana Ajani. All rights reserved.</rights>
  
  <entry>
  <title type="text">new blog, who dis?</title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://localhost:3000/post1.html" />
  <id>http://localhost:3000/post1</id>
  <published>2017-05-19T00:00:00Z</published>
  <updated>2017-05-19T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <content type="html"><![CDATA[ <h2 id="hello-world">Hello world!</h2>

<p>Welcome to my blog! I’ve been meaning to get into the habit of writing <strong>consistently</strong>, so I added this section to my personal site in hopes of updating it every so often. Wrapping up my third year in college, I realized that I am currently living in the <strong>best time of my life</strong>. I’ve had some incredible opportunities, like studying abroad, interning at one of the largest tech companies, meeting so many awesome people at school, and I wished I had written down my stray thoughts during all these triumphs, failures, and comings and goings. I’ve made numerous attempts to keep a personal journal and I find that I am only able to keep up with it in streaks. So this summer, my goal is twofold:</p>

<ol>
  <li>
    <p>Keep a personal journal.</p>
  </li>
  <li>
    <p>Write regularly on this blog.</p>
  </li>
</ol>

<p>Both of these are ways for me to resume writing again. I like to think I’m a good storyteller in person, but there’s something about being able to convey the same story in writing that I’d like to improve upon. For the last few days, I’ve kept my journal near my bedside table and committed to writing in it before I go to sleep. Initially, I was unsure if I’d have anything worthwhile or “important” to write about. But I found that as soon as I started writing even a few thoughts about my day, more just starts flowing out and I’m able to keep writing. I think this will be beneficial because it will allow me to pin down exactly what I’m thinking or doing and why; it’ll allow me to be more conscious and deliberate. Socrates once said, “The life which is unexamined is not worth living” – I think spending a few minutes to organize my thoughts and assign meaning to them will be fulfilling. I can imagine that down the road, even the most banal commentary about work, school, music, friends, etc would be fascinating for future Sana to read through and get a sense of the headspace I was in during the “best years” of my life.</p>

<p>I’ve also been wanting to keep an online blog for a while, but I think I was a bit afraid of putting my opinions out there to be read by anyone and being judged for it. But now, I’ve come to realize that this is something that everyone who creates anything may worry about, but it doesn’t stop them. So, it’s not going to stop me either. I’ll post about new tech I’m learning, by myself or at school/work, current events in politics (oh gosh, I have many things to say about this), dope jams I’m listening to, and just random observations or questions I have. I’m excited for this new blog and this summer, so here goes :)</p>
 ]]></content>
</entry>



</feed>
